{
    "id": "15cfc37a50474494a1233e56447dbd37",
    "title": "Adverbs With Two Forms",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sorry I didn’t turn up – I ……………….. forgot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "clean",
                "cleanly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "At least ten children were ……………….. injured in the accident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "deadly",
                "fatally"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The comedy show was ………………….. amusing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "highly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The protestors demanded that the culprits should be ………………….  punished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "justly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t been to the theater much ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Isn’t she dressed …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettily"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be there at six o’clock ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sharp",
                "sharply"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Their door was ………………… open but nobody was inside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wide",
                "widely"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. believed that she loved me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrong",
                "wrongly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate arriving …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}